icici lombard and cnbc tv 18 present
india risk management awards risk master
class
the impact of kuwait 19 is uh not only
uh restricted to the health related
ailments
but in fact it has changed the way in
which we have uh you know we interact
travel
you know work uh and in fact it has also
led to the emergence of a lot of new
risks
you know cyber attacks it has become
much more common uh today when when you
know digitization is becoming a way of
life if you look back into history you
know where you know various
economies have been hit by some major
global catastrophic events
uh you know insurance industry globally
has always come out with
various solutions which can help the
economy to come back on its feet
you know post 9 11 you know that led to
a creation of the terrorism risk school
which ensured affordable prices and
adequate covers for protection against
terrorism risk the industry is already
working on
um in close coordination with the
government on developing a pandemic risk
pool
which would cover risks such as business
interruption unemployment etc
icici lombard and cnbc tv 18 present
india risk management awards risk master
class